

With a background spanning over 5 years across various IT project roles, and having earned a (French) state-recognized diploma as a React Developer, I am primed to lend my investigative spirit in addressing your unique challenges in the field of web development.



Warsaw



+48 727 780 075



zurek.katarzyna@gmail.com



github.com/Kasia307584



Katarzyna Zurek



<u>Portfolio</u>

Expertise















React.js - Redux - JavaScript - Html -Css - Bootstrap - Sass - Git - GitHub npm

Languages

French - fluent

6 years of active use in France including professional jargon and extensive use in social contexts until now

English - proficient

able to communicate easily and read technical documentation

Polish - native

Interests

Paraglider pilot

Ladies of Code associative project

Katarzyna Żurek

React Developer



HR app | Redux | React-Bootstrap www.wealth-health.app

- switch from jQuery to React to reduce tech debt
- NPM package release
- performance tests (Lighthouse)
- code documentation

Sports analytics | Recharts

www.sport-see.app

- advanced graphics using JS library Recharts
- ensure the quality of an application's data by creating a dedicated API call service

Banking app | Redux | REST API

www.argent-bank.app

- API authentication and authorization
- API REST design (with Swagger)
- state management with Redux

Apartment rental | React-Router www.kasa.app

- vvvvv.kasa.app
- JSON data useresponsive application

• routing with product ID

Experience

O JavaScript React Developer

2021 - now

Freelance projects

Developed multiple bachelor's and personal projects utilizing JavaScript, React, testing frameworks, and Node.js for backend development.

Web Content Manager

2019 - 2021

Emma Lavelle Co. | Madrid | Remote

Managed English learning platform built from Squarespace CMS website builder.

Consultant in IT projects

2014 - 2018

IT-NewVision | Suez, Enedis as clients | Paris

roles: Business Analyst, PMO, Financial and Business Controller

Different roles in large-scale digital transformation projects for French companies operating in the utility sector, and a lead role in ERP SaaS implementation at the parent company, IT-NewVision.

O Project Manager Assistant

2013

Crédit Agricole Technologies I Paris

Education

JavaScript React Developer

2021 - 2023

Bachelor (OpenClassrooms, France)

Professional diploma referenced by the French state and issued by the largest European online school. The program is fully project-oriented with 14 professional projects and support from an experienced mentor.

Organizational Consulting and Change Management

Master (University of Paris 8, #47 of 224 in France)

Sociology, Literature and Linguistics

2011

2013

Master (University of Wroclaw, Poland)